electricrun.com 2017-10-12

# Privacy Policy - Electric Run

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register for an event, respond to a survey, join our VIP list or fill out a form on our website.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To personalize your experience** (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * **To improve our website** (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * **To improve customer service** (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * **To process  transactions**  
_Your  information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested._
  * **To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**
  * **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, The DART cookies may also be used by us for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). The cookie is used to serve your specific ads and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served are to be targeted on the basis of your previous browsing history (For example, if you are viewing sites for visiting Las Vegas, you may also see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as a hockey site). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”, which does NOT track your personal information, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.If you would like to “opt out” of receiving online advertisements from us, please follow the instructions on the links below:

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information except as set forth in the Privacy Policy. We share end-user data with Major League Baseball Properties, Inc. and MLB Advanced Media, L.P., for Miami in 2017. We also disclose personally identifiable information to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please contact us for more info on the Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at info@electricrun.com.
